<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<deployment name="EmulatorDemo" divider="606" width="617" height="727" zoom="1.0" scroll-x="0" scroll-y="0" expand-description="false">
  <description>
    <![CDATA[A demonstration of the SPOT Emulator. Press the "Deploy & Run All" button 
below to get started. Then try out the various MIDlets described below.]]>
  </description>
  <spots>
    <role name="Sample MIDlets" show-role="true" expand-description="true">
      <project file="build.xml"/>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[A series of sample MIDlets to demonstrate the SPOT Emulator.

Right click on a virtual SPOT in the SPOT View to get a menu of 
possible commands. Select "Run MIDlet" to get a list of available
MIDlets to be run. Right click on the MIDlet's name to get a popup
to "Exit" a running MIDlet.

SensorChecker
------------

This MIDlet demonstrates how the Virtual Sensor Panel can be used
in the SPOT World Emulator to interact with a virtual SPOT.
Use the Virtual SPOT's pop-up menu to display the sensor panel.
 
The LEDs on the virtual SPOT display the value read from one
of the SPOT's sensors.

There are four different modes:

 1. Display the light sensor reading in white
 2. Display the temperature sensor reading in red.
 3. Display the analog input A0 in green.
 4. Display the Z acceleration in blue.

As you move the appropriate slider in the sensor panel you will 
see a change in the LED display.

Pushing the left switch (SW1) advances to the next mode.
The current mode is shown by setting one of H0-H3 to high.

Also D0 is set as an output and the application sets it
to mirror the value that D1 is set to.


Sawtooth
-------

A very simple MIDlet to turn on the LEDs one by one,
each brighter than the previous until they are all on.
Then all the LEDs are turned off and the cycle repeats.


Count
-----

A simple MIDlet that uses the left switch (SW1) to set the color of the LEDs
and the right switch (SW2) to count in binary in the LEDs.


BroadcastCount
-------------

A simple MIDlet that uses the left switch (SW1) to broadcast a message
to set the color of the LEDs of any receiving SPOTs and the right 
switch (SW2) to count in binary in its LEDs.

Messages received from the other SPOTs control the LEDs of this SPOT.

If a shared basestation is available a real SPOT can interact with the
virtual SPOTs via the radio.


UnicastCount
-------------------

A simple MIDlet that pairs two SPOTs so each controls the others LEDs.
The left switch (SW1) sends a message to set the color of the LEDs of
its paired SPOT and the right switch (SW2) to count in binary in its LEDs.

Messages received from the other SPOT controls the LEDs of this SPOT.

Even addresses pair with smaller odd addresses, & odd addresses pair
with larger even addresses.]]>
      </description>
    <spot address="VirtualSPOT" collapsed="false" show-status="false">
        <map-position x="200" y="300"/>
        <location value="in Emulator"/>
      </spot>
    <spot address="VirtualSPOT" collapsed="false" show-status="false">
        <map-position x="200" y="300"/>
        <location value="in Emulator"/>
      </spot>
    <spot address="VirtualSPOT" collapsed="false" show-status="false">
        <map-position x="200" y="300"/>
        <location value="in Emulator"/>
      </spot>
    <spot address="VirtualSPOT" collapsed="false" show-status="false">
        <map-position x="200" y="300"/>
        <location value="in Emulator"/>
      </spot>
    </role>
  </spots>
  <host-apps>
  </host-apps>
</deployment>
